A Guide to the San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records, 1931-2008 (bulk 1985-2005)
San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Records
- Photographic Materials
  - Events (Box 15)
    - La Prensa Comedy Jam, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - President's Council Luncheon Bexar County Legislators, March 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - President's Council, June 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - President Council Series, May 1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Press Conference, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Primera Reunion Trilateral de Camaros de Comercio, undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Proofs for Publication, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Prospective New Member Orientation, February 1996 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Radio, Television Events, undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Reception for Bill Richardson, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Ribbon Cutting, October 2002 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Ribbon Cutting, August 25, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Ribbon Cutting, January 25, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Ribbon Cutting, November 16, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Ribbon Cutting, November 18, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Ribbon Cutting, October 26, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Ribbon Cutting YMCA, September 1998 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ribbon Cutting, Accent Int'l Realty, early 1996 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Accounting Solutions, January 17, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Alamo Parking Corp., May 12, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Albertson's, undated (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Arrow, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Beatriz Salon, April 14, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Blossom Athletic Center, May 17, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Ribbon Cutting – C amp;amp; C Realty, undated (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Champs Medical, January 15, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Cingular Wireless, May 3, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Ribbon Cutting Ceremony Culligan, early 1996 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Culligan, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Delladel, undated (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Ribbon Cutting – 5.0 Sportswear, September 25, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Ribbon Cutting – 4 Season Radiator, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Ribbon Cutting Health Line Health Humana, July 1996 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Ribbon Cuttings – KB Homes, etc. (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Las Palapas, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Ribbon Cutting – LNB, August 3, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Lowe's, June 19, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Lowe's, November 2001 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Metropolitan Methodist Hospita, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Mexico's Best, Inc., undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Money Management International, September 1999 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Ribbon Cutting – On the Border, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Palo Alto Caf?undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Pollo Loco, May 17, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Po-Po's, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Ribbon Cutting – RC's BBQ, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Robert Half Internation, March 27, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Rosa Verde Health Group, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Ribbon Cutting - Rosario's, early 1996 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Ribbon Cutting – San Antonio Housing Authority, January 25, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Satellite Theater, November 18, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Santa Clara, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Sissi's Gifts, December 1999 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Ribbon Cutting – State Farm Insurance, May 10, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Tire's and Llantas, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Ribbon Cuttings – Unidentified, March 6, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Unidentified, July 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Unidentified, September 1998 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Unidentified, undated (Box 22, Folder 9-14)
    - Ribbon Cutting – Verizon Wireless, January 18, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - River Parades, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - River Parades Pachanga, April 1998 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - River Parade Pachan, April 21, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - San Luis Trade Mission, June 1996 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - School Events, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sea Island, June 26, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Sea World Reception, March 3, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Senator Frank Madia Lunch/LSA, July 1998 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Senator Frank Madia Luncheon, July 1997 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Sheraton Gunter Sponsors Emerging Issues Forum, June 21, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Shoppers Special, undated (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Small Business Awards, May 15-16, 21, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Small Business Forum, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Small Business Forum, April 17, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Small Business Forum, May 22, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Small Business Forum, June 1997 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Small Business Forum, September 1996 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Small Business Forum, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Small Business Forum Breakfast, October 1997 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Small Business Forum Breakfast – Finale, November 1997 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Sporting Events, undated. (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Spurs Mixer, February 1998 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Spurs Mixer, February 29, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Staff Christmas Card, undated (Box 50)
    - Staff Development Day, May 11, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Star Enterprise Grant, February 1998 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Stock Show Events, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - St. Patrick Mixer, March 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Superintendent Luncheon, March 31, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Superintendent Luncheon, August 1996 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Tejano Music Award Kickoff and Networking Mixer, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Frank Tejeda Event, August 23, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Telethon – Navideno, October 18, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce Conference, July 1996 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce Convention, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Texas Association of Mexican-American Chambers of Commerce Convention, July 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Texas Cavalier's River Parade SAHCC River Parade International Fiesta, April 1997 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Texas – NAFTA, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Thanks for Traveling, October 2001 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Think Big/Buy Small Campaign, January 26, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Tourism Development Conference, undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - US-Mexico Economic Outlook Conference, undated (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Visiting United States Presidents and Family Members, Congressmen, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Volunteer Committees, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Washington DC – Meetings/SAHCC Delegation, September 26, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Welcoming Vice President of Costa Rica, undated (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Assorted event photographs (Box 49-50)
    - Unidentified Aerial Photos, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Award Ceremonies, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Events, Banquets, Parties, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Event – Proofs, March 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Events – Black and White, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Places (Box 24)
    - Alamo Quarry, undated. (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Elemdorf Lake Park (before and after photographs), 1951 - 1952 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Stores, Buildings, Signage, undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Work Environments, undated. (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Queretaro, Mexico, March 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Spoetzl Brewery, undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Rooms, undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified photograph album, undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbooks (Box 27)
    - 1980-1992 (Box 27)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 28)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 29)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 30)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 31)
    - 2000-2001 (Box 32)
    - 2001-2003 (Box 33)
  - Unidentified Photographs (Box 25-26)
- Audiovisual and Digital Materials
  Materials are organized by format. Events covered on the recordings include speeches, award programs, interviews and news coverage.
  RESTRICTED: Original audiovisual materials and digital format materials are closed to patron use.
  - Audiocassettes (Box 13)
    - Radio Unica, undated (Box 13)
    - Past Chairs Reception, 1996 (Box 13)
    - Unidentified (3 cassettes), undated (Box 34)
    - Board Meeting, May 5, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Executive Board Meeting, May 28, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, June 11, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Executive Board Meeting, June 25, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, July 9, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Executive Board Meeting, July 23, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, August 13, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Executive Board Meeting, August 27, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, September 10, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Executive Board Meeting, September 24, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, November 12, 1991 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, January 7, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Hispanic Board Retreat, January 11, 1992, [ Tapes 1-3 ] (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, February 11, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, March 10, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, August 11, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, September 8, 1992 (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1992, [ Part 1 ] (Box AV3)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1992, [ Part 3 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, October 13, 1992, [ Part 4 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, November 24, 1992, [ Part 1 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, January 11, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1993, [ Part 1 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, February 9, 1993, [ Part 2 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, March 9, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, June 8, 1993, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, July 13, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, September 14, 1993, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, October 19, 1993, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Special Call Board Meeting, October 29, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Executive Board Meeting, November 23, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, November 30, 1993 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, February 8, 1994 (Box AV4)
    - Current Members, San Antonio, Texas, March 17, 1994 (Box AV4)
    - Non-Current Members, San Antonio, Texas, March 17, 1994 (Box AV4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, December 2, 1994 (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, December 13, 1994, [ Tape 2 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting "Special", January 19, 1995, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, February 14, 1995, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, February 16, 1995, [ 3 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 14, 1995, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, April 18, 1995, [ Tape 1 ] (Box AV4)
    - Board Meeting, May 16, 1995 (Box AV4)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 13, 1995 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, July 25, 1995 (Box AV5)
    - MDBF, September 15, 1995 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, September 19, 1995, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 14, 1995 (Box AV5)
    - Last Board Meeting, November 21, 1995, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 10, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, January 24, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, February 14, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, February 27, 1996, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, March 27, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 10, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, April 24, 1996, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting at Valero, May 22, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 12, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, June 26, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, July 24, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 10, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 21, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, August 28, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, September 17, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, October 9, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, October 30, 1996, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at VIA, November 13, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting, November 20, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at Mario Barrera's Office, December 11, 1996 (Box AV5)
    - First Board Meeting at YMCA, January 22, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, February 12, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting at Frost Bank, February 26, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 12, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting at Nations Bank, March 26, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at San Antonio Hispanic Chamber Commerce, April 9, 1997 (Box AV5)
    - Board Meeting at Frost, April 23, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, May 14, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting at Consul's Office, May 28, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, June 11, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting at Frost Bank, July 1, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Board Meeting, July 30, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 13, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting at South Western Bell, August 27, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, September 9, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting, September 24, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, October 9, 1997 (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting at Bank One, October 22, 1997, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV6)
    - Executive Committee Meeting at San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, November 12, 1997, [ 2 tapes ] (Box AV6)
    - Board or Executive Meeting, Dec-97 (Box AV6)
    - Board meeting, December 16, 1998 (Box AV6)
    - Board of Directors 11/18, undated (Box AV6)
    - 1st Lionel Sosa Meeting with Staff, undated (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting 5/11, undated (Box AV6)
    - Board Meeting 5/14, undated (Box AV6)
    - Banquet Mexican Chambers, undated (Box AV6)
    - Noche De Amor- PSA, undated (Box AV6)
    - Untitled, May 1, 1996 (Box AV6)
    - Untitled, undated, [ 8 tapes ] (Box AV6)
  - Microcassette (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 11, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, April 23, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, May 9, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, May 23, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, June 13, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 27, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 11, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, July 25, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 8, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, August 29, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, September 12, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, September 19, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, October 10, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, October 30, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, November 14, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, November 28, 2001 (Box AV8)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of commerce Strategy Session, December 4, 2001, [ 3 Cassettes ] (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee and Board of Directors Meeting, December 12, 2001, [ 2 Cassettes ] (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, January 9, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, January 23, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, February 20, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, February 27, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, March 13, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, March 27, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, April 10, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, April 16, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, May 22, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, June 26, 2002, [ 2 Cassettes ] (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, July 10, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, August 14, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Staff Strategy Session, August 29, 2002, [ 2 Cassettes ] (Box AV8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, September 25, 2002 (Box AV8)
    - Untitled, Undated, [ 4 Cassettes ] (Box AV8)
  - VHS (Box 35)
    - Nuestra Camara, February - March 1988 (Box 35)
    - Bailando Show, June 15, 1989 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Census, 1990 (Box 35)
    - "Morelos y sus Atractivos Turisticos," August 1991 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce Presentation, June 12, 1992 (Box 35)
    - Economic Development Foundation "Logic and Lifestyle," August 21, 1992 (Box 35)
    - News Coverage: S.A.H.C.C., December 17, 1992 amp;amp; January 12, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Puntos de Vista, February 1993 (Box 35)
    - Puntos de Vista, February 22, 1993 (Box 35)
    - S.A.H.C.C., May 26, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Aircheck Interview Rick Gonzales, July 9, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Aircheck Hispanic Chamber Announcement, July 9, 1993 (Box 35)
    - Kelly Air Force Base News Report, June 1994 (Box 35)
    - President Clinton Tribute to Henry Gonzalez, October 21, 1994 (Box 35)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Welcome, 1996 (Box 35)
    - Junior Achievement. Yesenia Cardenas Speech, July 27, 1996 (Box 35)
    - Greater Dallas Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 60 yr. Video, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Noche de Gala, 1999 (Box 35)
    - 70th Anniversary of S.A.H.C.C. Banquet, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 1999 Business Achievement Awards, 1999 (Box 35)
    - Moving Beyond, 2000 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, January 7, 2000 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, January 7, 2000 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce (5 copies), January 10, 2000 (Box 35)
    - Emerging Business Award Winners, 2001 (Box 35)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Honors Alexander E. Briseno "A Word of Thanks" (Copy), March 9, 2001 (Box 35)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Honors Alexander E. Briseno- "A Word of Thanks" (Master), March 9, 2001 (Box 35)
    - Making Sense of the Numbers Census, May 8, 2001 (Box 35)
    - Cisneros, KSAT/ "Good Morning America," September 6, 2001 (Box 35)
    - 2002 Business Awards, 2002 (Box 35)
    - Emerging Business Award Winners, 2002 (Box 35)
    - Commercials for Specific Members "Think Big Buy Small," January 14, 2002 (Box 35)
    - News 4 at 10pm, April 4, 2002 (Box 35)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Business Awards, Awards Presentation Video, 2003 (Box 35)
    - Eva Campbell Morales Welcomes 2003 Board of Directors Banquet, 2003 (Box 35)
    - Business Achievement Award Winner Bill Morrow, 2003 (Box 35)
    - Business Awards, 2003 (Box 35)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards, Johnny Hernandez, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards, Patricia P. Stout, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards, Olga Bernal Owens, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards, Jay Tope, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Patricia P. Stout, 2004 (Box 36)
    - Adrianna Pedraz Tribute Video, Commentary from business leaders in S.A., undated (Box 36)
    - Al Aguilar: Creative Civilization, undated (Box 36)
    - Alicia Guerra, Gentlemen speaks about good qualities of Ms. Guerra, undated (Box 36)
    - C/NET Titles. How Brad/Ives Designs, undated (Box 36)
    - Credits, Take No. 2, undated (Box 36)
    - El Corazon de San Antonio, undated (Box 36)
    - First Business News Program, news piece on running U.S military like a business, undated (Box 36)
    - Gov. George W. Bush Address to S.A.H.C.C., undated (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber Banquet, 63rd Annual Banquet, undated (Box 36)
    - Hispanic Chamber Corp. Video (Original), undated (Box 36)
    - Janet Meza, Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 36)
    - La Hacienda Treatment Center (marketing videos), undated (Box 36)
    - Liz Torres Samples, undated (Box 36)
    - Mariachi USA Demo Tape, undated (Box 36)
    - McDonnell Douglas: Missile Systems, undated (Box 36)
    - OLE: Our Latin Experience, undated (Box 36)
    - Rick Montenovo, Commentary on Mr. M about his career, undated (Box 36)
    - Roscoe Red on Living WOAI, new Line of Clothing Based in S.A., undated (Box 36)
    - The S.A.H.C.C. Logo with Songs, undated (Box 36)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Promotional Video, undated (Box 36)
    - A Story of Betrayal Part II, U.S.C.C., Support Clinton's Tax Program, undated (Box 36)
    - To Live in America with Linda Tafolla, undated (Box 36)
    - Tribute to Janie at Alcion, undated (Box 36)
    - Winning the Race, American Firms vs. Global Markets, undated (Box 36)
    - Works of Television and film by Latina Actress Liz Torres, undated (Box 36)
    - San Antonio Mexican Chamber of Commerce Video, 1982 (Box AV1)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards: Patricia P. Stout, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - 75th San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: El Porazon de San Antonio, undated (Box AV1)
    - Justice for my People: The Dr. Hector P. Garcia Story, 2002, 2002 (Box AV1)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards: Olga Bernal Owens, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - Pure San Antonio: One Perfect Day, undated (Box AV1)
    - 2003 Hispanic Chamber Business Awards Spots 1-4, 2003 (Box AV1)
    - "El Corazon de San Antonio" Looping Title, January 26, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - "El Corazon de San Antonio" 14:10 Minutes, January 26, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - "El Corazon de San Antonio" 14 Minutes, January 27, 2004 (Box AV1)
    - Medical, Industrial, Technology (English/ Spanish), Loop, July 18, 2002 (Box AV1)
    - Hispanic Chamber, 2005 (Box AV1)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce 2004 Business Awards: Jay tope, 2004 (Box AV1)
  - U-Matic (Box 34)
    - S.A.H.C.C. 1990 Chamber Video, January 6, 1990 (Box 34)
    - 64th Annual Banquet., January 13, 1993 (Box 34)
    - 64th Annual Banquet., January 13, 1993 (Box 34)
    - Laura Salinas Demo Reel, February 4, 1993 (Box 34)
    - S.A.H.C.C. 1993 Campaign, March 8, 1993 (Box 34)
    - S.A.H.C.C. 1993 Campaign, March 8, 1993 (Box 34)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Demo of 5 English and 3 Spanish, March 23, 1993 (Box 34)
    - S.A.H.C.C. Demo of 5 English and 3 Spanish, April 7, 1993 (Box 34)
    - Banquet Video, undated (Box 34)
    - Credits, undated (Box 34)
    - Hispanic Chamber Logo, undated (Box 34)
    - Interviews, undated (Box 34)
    - Property of the S.A.H.C.C., undated (Box 34)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 34)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 34)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 34)
  - Beta Cam (Box 34)
    - Business Awards Banquet, 2003 (Box 34)
    - Texas Governor George W. Bush for Hispanic Chamber of Commerce, undated (Box 34)
    - Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: "Juntos/ English/FP" (SP S), April 10, 1996 (Box AV9)
    - San Antonio Hispanic Chamber of Commerce: "Medical, Industrial, Technology" in English and Spanish (SP S), October 23, 2002 (Box AV9)
    - El Corazon de San Antonio (SP S), January 27, 2004 (Box AV9)